Mr Celsius Ukpong has come to The Synagogue Church of all Nations to receive prayer
over the problem of a terrible skin disease.
Moving down his right leg, you begin to see the painful lesions,
discolorations and marks of the incredibly painful disease.
The skin affliction proceeds all the way down to the soles of his feet
which are raw and wounded in places where the disease has worn away the skin.
The horrible disease covers his entire foot,
right up to the ends of his toes and under the toenails.
In this condition, simple actions like sitting, lying down or walking become immensely discomfortable
and bathing becomes an unbearable torture.
Let us hear from Mr Ukpong how this has affected his life.
Please tell us your name, your age and where you are from.
Celsius Ukpong, I am from Akwa Ibom
state, I'm 43 years old.
What is the problem that has brought you to The Synagogue Church of All Nations today?
I've been having this skin disease.
And how has this problem affected your life?
It has affected my life in several ways.
For example, I am unable to go to work now; there is severe agonizing pain.
I have been on high pain killers without success.
I have been to several hospitals and several churches without a solution.
In fact, I am a walking corpse as I'm talking to you now because of the agonizing pain.
And now that you are here, what do you believe God Almighty is going to do for you?
I want to be healed completely from this malady.
HEALING TIME
I am a walking corpse, have mercy
on me. I have been suffering.
I have agonizing pains. I can't go to bed; I am a walking corpse.
All my veins are dead, and I have skin lesions all over my body.
They have refused to go.
They are so painful, so agonizing.
All over my skin. Right from here,
to all my toes, everything.
The healing is for the salvation of your soul.
This sickness is not meant to destroy you
but to strengthen your desire for God.
Okay, so that is it.
Stand up!
Prophet T.B. Joshua instructs Mr Celsius to rise to his feet
and ministers the Anointing Water to him with immediate effect.
Watch his face as the divine operation of the Holy Spirit uproots the cause of his problem
and casts it out through the Anointing Water.
God is busy using the medium of the Anointing Water
to transform his situation from sickness to good health.
If you look at him by faith, you will see something coming out.
Coming out like a flame.
Restoring him back to the original position in which God made him.
Look here! Put down your hands.
You are free!
To God be the glory.
I am healed. Thank You, Jesus!
Glory to God in the highest.
Mr Celsius Ukpong returned triumphantly to The Synagogue Church of All Nations
to declare the goodness and favour of the Lord in his life.
On the left, you can see how he came with a terrible skin disease all over his leg and foot.
And on the right, with his trousers rolled up,
you can see the now perfect condition of Mr Ukpong's body
after his encounter with Jesus Christ at The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
The skin of his feet is beautifully restored back to normal
and all signs of the inflammation and disease have completely gone.
And he sits peacefully without any agitation or discomfort.
Let's hear from him how he feels now.
My legs are normal. I feel no pain; there is nothing like pain.
How are you feeling now?
I'm okay, I'm all right.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
I am Celsius Ukpong.
I'm a barrister and solicitor of the Supreme Court of Nigeria.
I came to The SCOAN about three years ago
on this problem you saw on the screen - the problem of a skin disease.
The problem you saw there ravished my whole body.
If I had removed my clothes then, you could have seen the symptoms.
I had this intense Inflammation that tended to explode my right leg.
I could not eat, sleep or do other things I wanted to do.
If you saw it on the screen, there was a very dark spot there.
It was part of those diseases.
There was nowhere too big for me to go, and nowhere too small for me to go.
I did everything. I exhausted my native intelligence.
If you come to my house, you won't know I'm a lawyer.
you would think I'm a medical doctor because I bought many medical books,
trying to read in order to find solutions because I lost faith completely
in what the doctors could do.
Before I came to The SCOAN, I was on a cocktail of drugs.
When you are on a cocktail of drugs, it means everything has failed
so your doctors are trying to put things together to make you survive.
That was the situation I was in before I came here.
Nothing was working.
It was too agonizing.
When I came here and Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me,
immediately the disease, inflammation and agonizing pain vanished.
As I'm speaking to you now, nothing like that has resurfaced.
All the dark spots that were on my body have retreated and I am well and strong.
And I can attend to my duties as I used to do.
Happily testifying, Mr Celsius Ukpong removes his sock and shoe
to show the place where the skin disease had once been.
His skin has been restored through the miraculous power of our Lord Jesus Christ
through the Anointing Water.
When I came to Lagos, in fact, the pain was so much
that they brought a wheelchair to bring me down from the plane; I could not walk.
But all those things that I could not do, right now, I can do them again.
This is the leg; an evidence to show that those things are not flukes
and it was what I experienced before I came to this place.
I am free and able to do all those things I could not do.
Even my job that was on the line has been restored.
It is as if nothing had happened because at that time,
while the sickness was pursuing me this way, my job was on the line to be destroyed.
But all those things have returned completely.
I'm living my normal life.
Stamping his foot on the ground, Mr Celsius feels no pain.
He is healed indeed.
There is nothing wrong with this leg now.
I am free! Thank You, Jesus!
He walked to and fro smoothly and smartly,
with no fear of any pain or discomfort.
What a miracle.
There is nothing God cannot do,
especially if you are privileged to meet a genuine man of God.
I met the so-called witch doctors that
told me several things about this leg
but they could not profer solutions.
So when you face this kind of a storming blast,
what you should do is to seek out where you can have your salvation
through the instrumentality of a man of God.
Prophet T.B. Joshua is a jewel; people should listen to his counsel and accept his prayers
because whatsoever he says, that is how it will come to be.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
TT: Lizz Ndung'u 06/09/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 16/09/2018